<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
        <title>Jesus Center Ministry's Blog</title>
        <description>Jesus Center Ministry's Blog - Jesus Centre Ministry</description>
        <link>https://www.nagekar.com</link>
        <atom:link href="https://www.nagekar.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 15:26:10 +0300</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 15:26:10 +0300</pubDate>
        <ttl>60</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>The First Family</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Gen 4:1-8&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Lk 10:1&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    God is always interested in a family. God created a good family and had a plan that he was going to show his prosperity through this family,that he was going to rule over the world through this family.
    When a family decides to honour and remain with God, they experience favour and prosperity. May God use us to be his representatives in our families. God is annointing us to be rebuilders of the bridge of our families to our God. Let's be a people that God is counting on us. God has a lot of interest in our siblings, parents and family members. When we weep because of our families, God also weeps. May God help us to be the priests in our families.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Sometimes we make or say things that destroys the bridge between God and our families, that a time comes when God wants to bless our families but he finds hate, conflicts and violence in us.
    As the children were killing one another,Adam and Eve knew very well what the issue was. Abel and Cain killed themselves without knowing what caused the trouble, but Adam and Eve knew where their recklessness began.
    They spent their time in pleasure and the results were their children living with hate for one another. It is usually good to check what is going on with our families,and praying with them for their mistakes. God had mercy with Abraham and Eve,and blesses them with Seth.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    May God open another door to replace that which was destroyed because of our family faults. May every bridge that was broken in our families be rebuilt in Jesus name. God can raise us for others in our families. In our families,there is a certain seed that carries the annointing to destroy what the devil has done in our family. We cannot be any better without God ,without him we are nothing. Because of Enosh, men began to call one the name of the Lord.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Grace and peace be multiplied unto you. He appeared in the flesh, was vindicated by the spirit, was seen by the angels, was preached among the nations,was believed in the world, was taken up in glory.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Grace and peace be multiplied unto you. He appeared in the flesh, was vindicated by the spirit, was seen by the angels, was preached among the nations,was believed in the world, was taken up in glory.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                <link>https://www.nagekar.com/2018/08/The-first-family.html</link>
                <guid>https://www.nagekar.com/2018/08/The first family</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>God must know you as one of his.</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Isa 5:13&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God is concerned with a generation that knows him. God is speaking to us this morning that we have gone into captivity because we lack knowledge, knowledge of knowing him. In the Bible, “my people” has been highlighted more than a hundred and twenty times. It is a sad reality that there are some people who God does not recognize as his people. It is sad to be in church and not have the knowledge of God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our honorable men have gone to vanish.,the church is quiet because she has lacked her knowledge of what God wants.
May our names be registered in heaven as one of his. We have gone into captivity because we don’t know who blesses us, who protects us. Although God created all people, not all people are God’s people.
How do we enter into captivity?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Thought patterns- as a person thinketh, so he is. The way we think can let us into captivity. The thought s of defeat, witchcraft, fear, and failures. It locks us out of God’s presence. To change our thinking pattern takes real struggle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;When we think more about ourselves,and less about God.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;if you are thinking more about yourself in giving, going to fellowship, work and less about God, then you are in captivity. We live in a generation where Christians are so centered in themselves, what they will get after prayers, what will come to them in person when the come to fellowship. They complain so much about so little things. It extends to preachers that will talk about their cars, the houses they live in,the price of the suits they wear.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The state of not knowing God keeps us away from God. The fact that we are found in church does not guarantee us to be a people of God.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God must know us as one of his. He wants us to be one of his.The church is going into captivity,not caring what happens to the state of governance, when the constitution is being tampered with to displace the position of God, when the national anthem is being deviated from addressing God with a prayer….may our nation be built by God, let our church be known for knowing who God is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God knew David even before the king knew him. Most of us struggle so much to be known by men, recognition from the political class, and not God. A lot of us are trapped in speaking ill of other people because we fail to concentrate on our assignment here on earth. Let us be the best on what we are assigned, fixing our eyes on Jesus, knowing who we are in God. May we be delivered from the mentality of thinking that our knowledge of people will change our lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you become a person of God?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Love Agape love, Jn 13:34-35. Be a person that loves, let’s embrace and celebrate one another. Love brings multiplication.,it keeps no record of evil. It does not boast.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be people of a purpose- God identifies with a people of purpose, United, moving towards one goal. People of a purpose don’t quarrel,they hold a purpose together and work best in all they do.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be a person of character- our God has character, he is holy, he is kind, he is faithful, he is a giver. Phil 1:27. The real you is when you are all alone,where no one knows or sees you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have hope- Rom 12:12, be joyful in Hope, be a person that is full of hope of better days ahead. It is not over until God says so.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Consecrate yourself to God,- be led by the holy spirit, give yourself to God.Set yourself a part for God. 
Take God seriously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://www.nagekar.com/2018/07/God-must-know-you-as-one-of-his.html</link>
                <guid>https://www.nagekar.com/2018/07/God must know you as one of his</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Soul Tie</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gen 21:9&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;1 Sam 18&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the time, Abraham was so cautious not to break the bond with Hagar, until that that time that God intervened.
Soul tie is like a tag, an attachment or mutation like Ruth and Naomi.
Soul tie is something that needs to be prayed about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Signs of soul tie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Physically, emotionally or spiritually Abusive relationship,but you still hold on to it. Relationship where one hurts another one, handles one without respect. Everytime you are not comfortable in a relationship but you still hold on to it then it is an unhealthy soul tie. Be it in marriage, family, church or business, every relationship has to be respected.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You have left a relationship long ago, but you keep on thinking about the other person obsessively. It is a soul tie. You make decisions based on general stereotyping.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Whenever you do anything,make a decision or have a conversation,you see the people you once related with as if they are there looking at you, or there with you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;When you engage in a sexual relationship,may be your spouse, the picture of the other person comes,you visualize, it is a sign of a soul tie. It involves illegal fantasies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You take on the negative traits of the person that your soul is tied to,and take their offenses whether or not you agree with them. It’s like you begin to inherit the other person’s character. You defend your right to stay in a relationship even if it is carrying negative outcomes….&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://www.nagekar.com/2018/07/Soul-Tie.html</link>
                <guid>https://www.nagekar.com/2018/07/Soul Tie</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
